=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 5=
That technique of yours is amazing.
What else can you produce?
I can produce anything.
The Wind God Chronicle is born
of the Wind God's power.
No talismans needed.
Just speak the spell.
That's so cool!
When you have time, teach me!
This art is divinely bestowed.
It can't be passed on.
Stingy!
Just say you don't want to teach.
Your master said
you're stuck at some bottleneck.
Is it those mirrors?
How do you know that?
What did you see?
Nothing much.
Just a woman.
Is she your beloved?
Hey, I am asking you.
Ignoring me again? Boring.
(You're my beloved one.)
(You're not as terrible as I thought.)
(Somehow,)
(it'd be a shame to eat you now.)
So who is she?
Do you like her?
Where is she? What is her name?
Still ignoring me.
Fine.
I guess a Taoist like you
wouldn't know love anyway.
Today, I'll teach you
the most powerful spell.
One strike can conquer all.
One strike to conquer all?
I've never heard of such a spell.
The word "love"
is the most powerful spell.
Whether it's heaven
standing in your way,
or every human and demon against you,
if you shout it out, scream it out,
let it out loud,
that one strike can conquer all.
But I...
But what?
But... But...
If you don't speak up,
nothing will ever happen.
What, are you waiting for her
to fall from the sky
and land right in your arms?
(What if)
(she really did fall from the sky?)
(In this forest...)
(why is there such sorrowful
demonic energy?)
A little demoness
and a young Taoist.
What a lovely pair!
Little demoness,
let me tell you a story.
(Joy Spider, you carry
the Five-Colored Silk.)
(You must beware of humans.)
(Their greed knows no bounds.)
(They'll skin you alive for your silk.)
(Beware of humans.
Especially the handsome ones.)
Miss.
I came to the mountains to paint.
I was so captivated by your beauty
that I painted you.
Please don't be upset.
I'm not. I love it.
If I may be so bold,
I see you're all alone,
and a seesaw is no fun by yourself.
May I join you?
Yes.
Darling, how do I look in this?
It's beautiful.
So beautiful.
Darling, I'm a demon.
Are you truly not afraid?
I am not.
Whether you're human or demon,
it is you whom I love.
If my true form is exposed
and the world rejects me, what then?
The world doesn't know your worth.
That's their loss.
If this place won't have us,
I'll take your hand
and wander the world.
There will always be a place for us.
This life is fleeting,
but my love for you will never fade.
Truly?
Truly.
This Five-Colored Silk
is woven from my Demon Essence.
Only one strand a year.
Darling, every year from now on,
I'll weave you a garment
with my Demon Essence
and blood as thread.
May we
be together forever.
Honey!
Run away!
What is wrong?
Some Taoists are coming to hunt demons.
You need to leave.
What about you?
I've already married you.
I've broken their rules.
Go! I'll hold them off.
They won't do much to me.
No!
I won't leave you.
Demon, die!
Come at me!
Don't hurt my husband!
Honey!
Darling!
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I am fine.
Are your
skin and threads harmed?
Look! Look!
This is a demon!
Get out of our village!
Demons deserve to die!
Serves her right!
The silks of the Wrath-Peak Spider
cannot be burned or soaked.
It shimmers in five colors.
Woven into clothing,
it will never fade or rot
for ten thousand years.
Now that you're frozen,
I can draw silk from you endlessly.
Your threads of love
have woven the road to my success.
Did you ever,
even for a moment,
truly love me?
Of course I did.
Your love was the finest silk of all.
From now on,
I'll never have to endure
that disgusting demon stench of yours.
Then I have no regrets.
What... what is this?
This...
Help!
The demon is eating people!
Run! Run!
Help!
Run! There is a demon!
Run!
In this mortal world,
no man will ever truly love a demoness.
(Love is a blade.)
(The cruelest of all.)
(Only by loving yourself)
(can you survive in this world.)
Where are we?
You are awake.
I just...
had a very strange dream.
What dream?
Thank you
for giving me a beautiful dream.
(In the end,
humans and demons are different.)
(From now on,)
(I will never miss another chance
to kill you.)
Is that so?
Then I hope you have beautiful dreams
every day.
(And you will never become
my nightmare again.)
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down;
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter
the hollow fate they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪